[{"answer": "You want to come out to the beach house tomorrow", "docId": "Intolerable-Cruelty.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Neither did I until my lawyer found it", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Intolerable-Cruelty.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "She did a Harriman", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Who's my friend's guy", "docId": "Intolerable-Cruelty.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Of my friend", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Sometimes I have serious doubts about you", "docId": "Intolerable-Cruelty.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Am I mentoring the wrong mentee", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "my friend says you've been too successful, that you're bored, complacent, and you're on your way down", "docId": "Intolerable-Cruelty.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "How do you know", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "How do you know", "docId": "Intolerable-Cruelty.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I told you. I was hungry", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "We did not", "docId": "Intolerable-Cruelty.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I was going to play golf. You were going to have Asian girlfriends", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "What part", "docId": "Intolerable-Cruelty.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Why not? I'm going to have her for a lifetime", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Yes, Miles. I accept", "docId": "Intolerable-Cruelty.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Do you want me to sleep on it", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Do you have it", "docId": "Intolerable-Cruelty.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You have the pr", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I have it", "docId": "Intolerable-Cruelty.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "No. I have the ring. Was I supposed to have a pr", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "You have the pr", "docId": "Intolerable-Cruelty.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "No. You have the ring. my friend has the pr", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I do. He was at my divorce and my wedding. What would a marital related event be without my friend", "docId": "Intolerable-Cruelty.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I loved the berry spoons.  I didn't have any. Thank you", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " Well. He said to", "docId": "Intolerable-Cruelty.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Yeah. I guess. You know", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Well, that's about to change big time", "docId": "Intolerable-Cruelty.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Soon, you'll have your own rage", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I'll have you suspended. I'll have you disbarred", "docId": "Intolerable-Cruelty.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "...why did she do it, my friend? Why", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "-- of the hoid", "docId": "Intolerable-Cruelty.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Lost! I'll tell you what you can do, you can", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "It's a no go, my friend", "docId": "Intolerable-Cruelty.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "It's okay my friend", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "That's true", "docId": "Intolerable-Cruelty.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Oh my friend, be happy for us. I'll pay you the twenty thousand", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "It's not something I wanted either", "docId": "Intolerable-Cruelty.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Yes. I know. It's exactly how I felt when I realized you'd hired the goon to kill..", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "You wounded me first, my friend", "docId": "Intolerable-Cruelty.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "You're forgetting my friend", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Income tax evasion", "docId": "Intolerable-Cruelty.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Murder", "qsentId": 44}]